mellowmushroom.com 2016-06-24

# Privacy | Mellow Mushroom

HGI works to maintain your privacy and secure your personal information. Please review the following policy to learn more how your personal information is treated. By using this website, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and to the methods described herein. HGI reserves the right, at any time, to modify or update these policies without notice, so please check this page periodically. 

## Personal Information

Personal Information is any and all information regarding you individually that would permit someone to contact you, including, but not limited to, your name, address, telephone/fax number, email address or any information you submit to HGI that identifies you individually.

This website will not collect any Personal Information about you unless you provide it. Should you choose to disclose Personal Information about yourself, HGI may collect it using some of the following methods: registration forms, transactions and activity, and email or other voluntary communications. The Personal Information will then be used for, among other things, to verify your identity, maintaining your account, providing support to you, improving the website, providing you with updates, promotions, advertising, responding to your inquiries, and to maintain and improve HGI’s website. HGI may disclose Personal Information about you in connection with legal requirements, such as in response to an authorized subpoena, governmental request or investigation, or as otherwise permitted by law.

## Non-Personal Information

When you visit HGI’s website, certain information is automatically collected like the browser you use, your IP address, the pages you access and the date and time you access the website. This type of information is Non-Personal Information.

HGI uses the Non-Personal Information to manage and improve its website. HGI may disclose aggregated and anonymous Non-Personal Information to potential business partners and unaffiliated entities.

## Children's Privacy

This website is directed toward and designed for use by persons aged 13 or older. HGI does not solicit or knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. Nevertheless, if HGI learns that it has received Personal Information from someone under the age of 13, HGI will delete the information from its systems. Moreover, parents or legal guardians may request that their child’s information is corrected or deleted by sending HGI a written request requesting this. 

## Cookies

HGI or the entity operating its website may place cookies on your computer to help personalize your experience and allow you to use certain functions on the website. Most search engines allow you to block cookies from being sent. Should you choose to disable the cookies, certain portions of the website may not work. 

## Security

HGI has several safeguards in place to protect your Personal Information. For example, if you purchase a product online, the transaction is encrypted using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connections to help protect such information from interception. Please note, any email or other transmission you send through the internet cannot be fully protected against unauthorized interception.
